In the future, the odds of survival are 1000 to 1.
That's just the way she likes it.
Tank Girl is a action, comedy, science fiction film directed by Rachel Talalay.
After a comet disrupts the rain cycle of Earth, the planet has
become a desolate, barren desert by the year 2033.
With resources scarce, Kesslee, head of the powerful and evil Water & Power
Corporation, the de facto government, has taken control of the water supply.
Unwilling to cower under Kesslee's tyrannical rule, a pair of outlaws known as Tank Girl and Jet
Girl rise up, joining the mysterious rebel Rippers to destroy the corrupt system.
Rebecca / Tank Girl, played by Lori Petty.
Jet Girl, played by Naomi Watts.
Kesslee, played by Malcolm McDowell.
T-Saint, played by Ice-T.
Booga, played by Jeff Kober.
Deetee, played by Reg E. Cathey.
Tank Girl is a 1995 American post-apocalyptic science fiction film
directed by Rachel Talalay and written by Tedi Sarafian.
Based on the British comics series created by Jamie Hewlett and Alan Martin, the
film stars Lori Petty, Naomi Watts, Ice-T, and Malcolm McDowell.
Set in a drought ravaged Australia years after a catastrophic impact event, it follows the antihero Tank Girl (Petty) as she, Jet Girl (Watts),
and genetically modified supersoldiers called the Rippers fight Water & Power, an oppressive corporation led by Kesslee (McDowell).
After reading an issue of the Tank Girl comic she had received as a gift, Talalay obtained
permission from the comic's publisher Deadline to direct a film adaptation.
She selected Catherine Hardwicke to be the production designer, and worked
closely with Martin and Hewlett during the making of the film.
Tank Girl was filmed primarily in White Sands, New Mexico, and Tucson, Arizona.
The film's critically praised soundtrack was assembled by Courtney Love, and the
Rippers' makeup and prosthetics team was headed by Stan Winston.
Winston's studio were so enthusiastic about the project they cut
their usual prices in half to meet the film's budget.
Financially unsuccessful, Tank Girl recouped only about $6 million of its $25
million budget at the box office and received mixed reviews from critics.
Martin and Hewlett have since spoken negatively of their experiences creating the film, and Talalay
blamed some of the film's negative reception on studio edits over which she had no control.
Despite the box-office failure of the film, it has since become a cult
classic and has been noted for its feminist themes.
The film explores themes of dystopia, destroy,
reincarnation, based on comic, desert.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.